https://homeopathycenter.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy Privacy Policy – Center for Homeopathy
Search for:
Menu
Join Login DONATE What is Homeopathy? Getting Started with HomeopathyPracticing & Studying HomeopathyHomeopathy FAQsHomeopathy StoriesResources Research on HomeopathyResearch ArticlesHomeopathy Research FAQQuotable Research LibraryFind a RemedyFind a HomeopathFind an OrganizationFind a SchoolFind a Retailer / WholesalerEducational MaterialsStudy GroupsGet Involved DonateVolunteerAdvertiseNCH & Homeopathic Service AwardsYour Homeopathy StoryNews & Events EventsJAHC ConferencePress ReleasesNews ArchiveAdvocacyBecome a Member Organizational MembersStudent MembersLifetime MembersProfessional MembershipIndividual MembershipAbout Board & StaffHomeopathic Action AllianceOur PartnersMember Resources e-Learning CenterMateria Medica and Repertory DatabaseHomeopathy TodayMember Only Webinars (login required1)My account
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which NCH collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.homeopathycenter.org website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by NCH.Personally identifiable informationWe may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personally identifiable information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personally identifiable informationWe may collect non-personally identifiable information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationNCH may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:· To improve customer serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.· To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.· To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.· To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include news, updates, related product or service information, etc.· To provide targeted services and contentHow we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sharing your personal informationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users personally identifiable information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personally identifiable information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.Third party websitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.Changes to this privacy policyNational Center for Homeopathy has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:NCH1120 Route 73, Suite 200Mt. Laurel, NJ 08054856.437.4752www.homeopathycenter.orginfo@homeopathycenter.org
What is Homeopathy?
Resources
Get Involved
1120 Route 73, Suite 200 Mt. Laurel, NJ 08054
info@homeopathycenter.org Charitable Solicitations Registration
Code of Conduct
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
© 2020 National Center for Homeopathy. All Rights Reserved.Websites for nonprofits
by Elevation Web
0
